

SEIYEFA GOODLUCK

+2349010197681 | **E:** Seiyefagoodluck1@gmail.com Lugbe, Abuja, FCT, Nigeria

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Motivated with developed business acumen and broad experience across Digital marketing and management roles. Highly adaptable and self-motivated leader with proven ability to manage diverse personalities. Offering strong social and creative skills to identify solutions to challenging problems. Collaborative team player with excellent interpersonal, communication and conflict resolution skills.

WORK HISTORY

CO- IT MANAGER

12/2019 - CURRENT

All Nations University | Koforidua, Ghana

- Managed day-to-day IT operations, including supervision and assignment delegation for a 5-member team.
- Addressed student issues to ensure aswift and successful resolution.
- Mitigated risk by ensuring regulatory compliance for required licensing.

ASSISTANT LECTURER

09/2019 - CURRENT

All Nations University | Koforidua, Ghana

- Taught 30 undergraduate classes per semester in Oil and Gas Offshore and Oil and Gas Economics.
- Provided tutelage to individuals and groups of 35 students through monitoring and evaluation.
- Developed and implemented lesson plans that covered the various offshore technologies used in the Oil and Gas Industry.

TUTOR

01/2019 - CURRENT

GAPBUSTER GHANA INC. | Koforidua, Ghana

- Coached and mentored trainee tutors on successful teaching strategies and time management.
- Provided early intervention assistance to struggling students not yet considered behind.
- Maximised student retention by providing an inclusive and stimulating learning experience, encouraging students to overcome challenges by recognising their efforts.

CEO

08/2018 – CURRENT

THE DIGITAL FUTURE LAB, INC. | ACCRA, Ghana

- Drove industry-leading profit increase by transforming production process and aligning sales targets to meet dynamic industry conditions.
- Communicated with clients to meet fiduciary obligations, strengthen relationships and define client objectives.
- Participated in labour contract negotiations with All Nations University to successfully achieve high student in takes through social media marketing.

Increased business profits by 70% through strategic updates.

TEACHING ASSISTANT

09/2017 - 09/2019

All Nations Univeristy | Koforidua, Ghana

- Partnered with teacher to plan and implement lessons following school's curriculum, goals, objectives and philosophies.
- Performed administrative activities such as taking attendance, marking assignments and maintaining student records
- Organised activities to drive social, emotional, physical and intellectual development.

SKILLS

- Customer rapport
- Opportunities identification and creation
- Diplomatic leadership
- Revenue growth
- Customer care

- Software Development (Front-end Developer)
- Digital Marketing
- Sales techniques
- Capital improvement planning
- Systems and automation applications

EDUCATION (

BACHELORS OF ENGINEERING degree | Oil And Gas

05/2017

Engineering

ALL ATIONS UNIVERSITY COLLEGE, Koforidua

- Elected to President for National Society of Black Engineers in 2016
- Graduated in Top 5% of Class
- Member of National Society of Black Engineers
- Graduated with a Second Class Upper